I was just here eating my night cheese and it's like, you ever seen something so racist that you'd be like, it's like you could feel the cotton in your throat.
Justin Pearson wasn't white. That's probably how he got into Bowdoin in the first place.
But he did a fantastic impression of it. What a nice young man.
Has he considered the apprenticeship program at Citibank?
Justin Pearson has changed quite dramatically, as you can see.
He transitioned from a crypto white kid into the modern incarnation of Martin Luther King Jr. himself.
It's remarkable, really. But you've got to ask yourself, as long as we're mimicking civil rights leaders who died almost 60 years ago, why not some variety?
You never see politicians transitioning to say Malcolm X. Why is that?
Maybe because Malcolm X didn't talk like a sharecropper. He spoke dignified standard English.
Y'all know there's times that you hear and see things over racist. You look around like.
Y'all heard that? Y'all saw that?
That's a whole network.
Mm-hmm.
What's comedy, though, is him saying, why aren't people impersonating Malcolm X?
Baby, you don't want Malcolm X.
What you need is a lot of Malcolm Little upside the head.